# REETIK PATEL

(479) 385-1212
reetikp@gmail.com
www.reetikpatel.me
www.linkedin.com/in/reetik

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

I am a full-stack engineer with a passion for creating intuitive, research backed user interfaces. The user always comes first! With over 7 years of building enterprise solutions, I emphasize maintainability and efficiency in my work. I'm able to pick up new processes and tools very quickly.

#### **SKILLS & TOOLS**

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

Typescript/Javascript	NextJS	User Experience (UX)	Azure
React	NodeJS	Sketch	Git
React Native	Vue	Figma	
HTML   CSS   SASS	Storybook	Adobe XD	

Kotlin / Java Tailwind

EDUCATION &

## UNIVERSITY OF ARKANSAS

Bachelor of Arts, Computer Science

Zeplin

Minor in Management

### NN/G UX MASTER

Specialties in Interaction Design and UX Research

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### XEROSEC LLC

Software Engineer | Jan 2024 - May 2024

- Designed, built, and released new frontend for a script sharing platform using NX monorepo and component library documented with Storybook
- Integrated authentication with Azure B2C
- Set up CI/CD pipelines with Github Actions

#### BILL.COM / DIVVY

Software Engineer | Oct 2022 - Dec 2023

- Built and released new budget tools including policy management and import functionality for budget groups
- Greatly improved test coverage and code readability
- Worked on migrating legacy Javascript monorepo to new federated Typescript repositories

## WALMART GLOBAL TECH

Software Engineer | Nov 2016 - Sept 2022

- Created an admin UI to manage an internal notification platform integrated into businessfacing mobile applications
- Applied UX practices in documentation and example projects for React Native, Android, and iOS SDKs
- Maintained the Apple code signing process for all internal iOS applications involving hundreds of certificates and profiles
- Applied CI/CD to streamline numerous support processes using Jenkins
- Worked with the AI & Machine Learning team on a React Native application to improve data entry
- Set up API secrets management workflows and updated SSL certificates
- Created API routes in NodeJS and Java Spring Boot backends
- Managed deployments to hybrid cloud infrastructure hosted on-prem and in Azure